

FahiraSocial Media Specialist | Content Strategist

085262774355

- fahira1678@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahira-iraa/
- Bandung, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

Lead of Social Media Specialist

Intelligo ID

10/2021 - Present

Become a position as Head of Division in the Social Media Team

- Responsible for handling all social media platforms
- Managing the related team
- · Created impactful content planners for social media
- · Developed engaging campaigns

Chairman of the Belawan Bahari Region Youth Forum Forum Anak Belawan Bahari

12/2018 - 01/2020

Directed a team to participate in multiple community projects.

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering

International Logistics and Business University 2024

Applied Bachelor Degree

Project:

Project I - Analysis of Midwife Clinic Information System Based on Website

Project II - Design and Development of Web-Based Clinic Information System Using Vue JS

Project III - Prediction of Pregnancy Diagnosis Using C4.5 and Random Forest Algorithm

Achievements and Awards:

Winner of Design Thinking in Character Building Event | 2020

PT Pos Indonesia Scholarship | 2021

Medan City Scholarship | 2022

Natural Sciences Major

SMA Negeri 19 Medan

2020

Senior Highschool

CERTIFICATES

Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate - SFPC

03/2022 - 03/2024

SUMMARY

Howdy, my name is Fahira. I have an interest in working in an adaptive and creative environment. Skilled in Analytical Thinking, Creative Thinking, Multitasking, Content Planning, and Social Media Fluency. Experienced in planning content and managing social media platforms for educational technology in the field of data science. Currently, I am an active student at International Logistics and Business University majoring in Informatics Engineering, while also building a small edutech startup as a Social Media Specialist at Intelligo ID.

SKILLS

Social Media Management

Content Creation

Social Media Data Analysis

Machine Learning

Looker Studio

Python

HTML, CSS

Github

Figma

Notion

Leadership

Teamwork

Public Speaking

Creativity

Communication

Critical

Decision Making

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native
English Basic